fontriver.com 2012-10-04

# FontRiver.com Help Center

FontRiver.com takes your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the Web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated directly by us, by our partner, or by our affiliate.

### Visitor Tracking

We sometimes collect anonymous information through the use of various technologies, possibly including one called "cookies," to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on FontRiver.com, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. This anonymous information is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data." FontRiver.com or its analytic vendors may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service.

Also, when we collect personal data, we may extract some information and combine it with other information, such as clickstream data. This information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your personal information used in this manner, you can opt-out by clicking on the link to our "Contact Us" page.

Cookies are small files that a Website installs on your hard drive. Cookies enable our Web server to recognize your computer. This allows a company to tailor its Websites to better match your interests and preferences. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the Websites visited just before and just after its Website.

You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to block cookies altogether. However, if you do so, your ability to use the Website may be impaired.

Most browsers also allow you to erase cookies already stored.

### Security

FontRiver.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Use of software author names, addresses and any other personal information is used only in our announcements and is not released to third parties nor do we send any mail to the return addresses offering or soliciting any services.

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. FontRiver.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.

### Contacting FontRiver.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via [online form](http://www.fontriver.com/contact/).
